developeranalytics.com 2016-10-18

# dA | social media ratings and report services

As of August 17, 2008

This Privacy Policy applies to developeranalytics.com ("Websites"). DeveloperAnalytics.com believes in the responsible use of personal information. 

**Developer Analytics Analysis Does Not Use Personal Data**

Sites within the Developer Analytics network provide us with anonymous social media usage data in accordance with their own privacy policies, which we aggregate and analyze to deliver content on our websites. All observed activity and interactions are anonymous, no personally identifiable information is used.

**Your Personal Information at DeveloperAnalytics.com's websites**

DeveloperAnalytics.com is the sole owner of the personal information collected on its Websites and we collect personal information from our users at several different points on these Websites. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Policy. 

DeveloperAnalytics.com's Websites ask for personal information only when it's necessary in order to deliver value-add service to you. We require certain pieces of information so we can provide you a personalized experience. For example, we require all registered members to provide an email address that we can validate and verify. 

**Cookies**

Be aware that our Websites use "cookies." Cookies are small packets of information we place on your hard drive for tracking purposes - essentially a code number that we use to recognize you when you come back to the site. Only the information you volunteer, however, or the choices you make while visiting the site, can be stored in a cookie. A cookie cannot determine your email address, for example, unless you type it in. Allowing a website to create a cookie does not give that or any other site access to the rest of your computer, and only the site that created the cookie can read it. 

Our Websites also use permanent cookies that store an encrypted session id code. This means we are able to "recognize" you when you come to the site (whether or not you have an account), without the need for you to log in. 

**Log Files**

We may also log IP addresses to track which users have made what page requests, what browser that person was using, what their cookie was, and at what time the request was made. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This logging process does not store any personally identifiable information. 

**Emails**

Administrative emails (like important changes to this privacy policy, for example) and all other emails will be sent to the email address provided for by the User. 

**Security Systems**

This website takes reasonable precautions to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices and are regularly reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

**Sharing**

We may share aggregated demographic information with our future partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

**Conflicts**

In the event of an inconsistency between these, this Privacy Policy and DeveloperAnalytics.com's "Terms of Service," the Terms of Service shall control. 

**Merger**

DeveloperAnalytics.com may assign any or all of its rights hereunder and may transfer data collected or acquired hereunder in the event of a merger or acquisition of all or substantially all of the assets of DeveloperAnalytics.com. 

**More information...**

If you wish to learn more about our privacy policies please contact [privacy@developeranalytics.com](mailto:privacy@developeranalytics.com) with the subject title "Privacy Policy." 

If we decide to materially change our privacy policy, we may notify users by way of an email. In the event that the DeveloperAnalytics.com, or a portion of its business is acquired, the acquiring party will only acquire your personally identifiable information subject to the terms of this privacy policy.
